<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Categories on Null's blog</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/categories/</link><description>Recent content in Categories</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>Page(/categories) (Nullrequest)</managingEditor><atom:link href="/categories/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Saying goodbye is hard</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/saying_good_bye_is_hard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 10:42:16 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/saying_good_bye_is_hard/</guid><description>before i continue i have to say i am sorry. Bye the time you read this i will most likly be dead. They&amp;rsquo;ll say it was sucide and it is. life is a rigged game. I am sick of always losing. I am sick of being useless. I have been living a lie for most of my life my parents have put me down for the last time. over the past year i met some people who really changed me for the better.</description></item><item><title>Self hosting part 2</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/self_hosting_part2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 15:21:57 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/self_hosting_part2/</guid><description>Background This is a continuation of the previous post. This will be part 2 of 3 hopefully if I can get my custom tools working. A lot has changed since last post. If you are reading this on the netlify subdomain please head over to http://nullrequest.com and continue reading. The linked website is currently running on my own hardware!!!!! Before I continue big thanks to sesa. She really helped my with my nginx configs.</description></item><item><title>Self hosting</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/self_hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 15:50:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/self_hosting/</guid><description>Background Recently I found out that my friend self hosted her website. I was actually pretty surprised this was possible. After finding out this was possible I began working on porting my blog to be run off netfliy and on my own servers. This is going to be my first long term project and series. I will be posting around once a month with updates and changes I will be implementing.</description></item><item><title>Arch install automation</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/arch_automation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 09:12:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/arch_automation/</guid><description>background I have a OEM desktop that I use as a headless(without a display) server. I found that I nuke this server very often when I mess something up and have to reinstall. With my recent move switching to Arch as my primary operating system. Reinstalling became a hassel. This post will take a diffrent approch. Rather then give instructions on how to make/build everything. I will talk about what I did and why I did that.</description></item><item><title>Ultimate arch linux setup</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/ultimate_arch_setup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:46:09 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/ultimate_arch_setup/</guid><description>Background Recently after distro-hopping I came back to Arch Linux. It was perfect for me and I really can&amp;rsquo;t move to another distro without missing the AUR. After installing Arch I went through a few extra steps to add some features like secure boot(I know its not needed) and Plymouth to add m to my setup. I am assuming you have used Linux this does not and will not replace the arch wiki.</description></item><item><title>How to setup Dockerised darkweb website</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/darkweb_website/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 12:59:28 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/darkweb_website/</guid><description>disclaimer I am not responsible if you break something. Please consult with your laws to see if using Tor is legal in your country. A example where it is not legal is China. In most countries it is legal but again please check you laws. This guide was written for Linux but may work on MacOS but will definitely not work on windows without some tweaks.
Background After my dockerised IRC project I realized that I wanted to host a website on the dark web.</description></item><item><title>How to setup a darkweb IRC</title><link>https://nullrequest.com/post/darkweb_irc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 13:00:24 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nullrequest.com/post/darkweb_irc/</guid><description>disclaimer I am not responsible if you break something. Please consult with your laws to see if using Tor is legal in your country. An example where it is not legal is China. In most countries it is legal but again please check you laws.
Background Before I get into how to set everything up. I am going to give some background on why I created this guide. Around 3 months ago a discord server I was on wanted to try and create an ultra secure Internet Relay Chat (IRC for short) server.</description></item></channel></rss>